(Raj:)Neener neener.
(Bernadette:)I brought sparkling cider.
(Sheldon:)Oh... the bubbles
tickle my nose.
(Sheldon:)I'll just open this now
so it can get
(Sheldon:)nice and flat
before we drink it.
(Bernadette:)So what do you want
to do tonight?
(Sheldon:)Oh, I have quite
the evening planned.
Our fetus-friendly
festival of fun begins
(Sheldon:)with an in-depth look
(Sheldon:)at the world of model trains,
(Sheldon:)and then we'll kick things
up a notch and explore
(Sheldon:)all the different ways
that you can make toast.
(Bernadette:)There's more than one?
(Sheldon:)You've heard of French toast?
Yeah.
(Sheldon:)Cinnamon toast?
(Sheldon:)Melba toast?
Yeah.
(Sheldon:)You get where I'm going here?
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Amy:)I'm getting
an earthy note.
(Penny:)Ah, there's
definitely some oak.
(Raj:)Also, uh, cherries?
(Leonard:)I smell nothing.
(Howard:)Really? Nothing?
(Leonard:)Just a... whole lot of Afrin.